ظآزA little bit sorry for my love for youظآز
ظآزSorry, I was a little lateظآز
ظآزI really want the unconscious longing
to appear fasterظآز
ظآزCan I get closer
and hear you say "I do" once moreظآز
ظآزHolding hands, the scenery
in midsummer is a new journeyظآز
ظآزThe chapters of a fairy tale
are performed one after anotherظآز
ظآزThe promised moment
will definitely not be forgottenظآز
ظآزCan I get closer and listen to
the frequency of your heartbeatظآز
ظآزStart the countdown 4321,
a new sceneryظآز
ظآزI want to see all the scenes about youظآز
ظآزNo need to miss you anymoreظآز
ظآزRight by your sideظآز
=Jin Secretary=
=Episode 13=
(Miss Jin, you've worked hard.
You can have a day off tomorrow.)
I got you here.
I came back for my phone.
Thank you. I'm leaving.
Wait.
- Anything to say?
- No.
Really?
I...
Lan Chen, who do you think you are?
Miss Jin, he's not a good person.
What?
Won't admit it?
He was the one who had me corner you.
What did you say?
Listen.
A grand group CEO hired someone
to intimidate his secretary.
Hmph.
What a despicable move.
What are you talking about?
It's getting interesting.
Acting now?
Amnesia?
The transfer record is on my phone.
Be our boss's girlfriend.
- Be his girlfriend.
Louder.
Did you hear that?
Who's so bold?
Daring to stir up trouble here.
Stop.
Let me take you home.
No need. I prefer riding a motorcycle.
ظآزSnapping out of it for a second, I want
to get away from this endless messظآز
ظآزLove is like a trap,
a carefully designed illusionظآز
ظآزWrite your name on the memories
that were once left behindظآز
ظآزThe once fleeting joy vanishedظآز
Miss Jin!
ظآزLove is like a meteor, taking away
the expectations and never coming backظآز
(Inpatient)
ظآزIts traces are etched in my memoryظآز
ظآزOnce again, I indulge in itظآز
What exactly did you just say?
(Chat records between CFO and Ling Feng)
I told you it was Lan Chen.
I was not lying.
This isn't Lan Chen's WeChat.
It's the CFO's.
Anyway, he is not a good person.
Are you?
You took the money to corner a girl.
Didn't I get beaten by you?
Give me the phone.
Seems these people
have long been targeting Lan Chen.
Now it's not just about the company.
It's personal grudges.
Okay, I got it.
Something happened
at the gym. I gotta go.
What do you want to eat for night snack?
I'll go buy it.
Oh, this bracelet is pretty nice.
Be careful. I'm leaving.
(Miss Jin, you've worked hard.
You can have a day off tomorrow.)
Why are you here?
I heard Mrs. Jin was hospitalized.
Of course, I should come.
Besides,
the person who upset her this time
wasn't me.
No need.
You're not welcome here.
Who would like to come here?
Besides,
I don't really like the smell of her.
I won't go in.
You'd better get out.
Me?
The one who should leave is you.
Because of your antics,
there's no way that Lan could get
investment from Lihuai International.
Are you satisfied?
What are you trying to say?
I advise you to leave Lan.
Even if I do it,
you still won't get him.
If I can't have him,
I'll destroy him.
No one can have him.
Listen,
you can't destroy
my man.
Dear journalists,
aren't you looking for Miss Jin?
She's here.
Why is it so noisy?
Quiet!
I am Miss Jin's sister.
ظآزI pass through the crowd with youظآز
ظآزAs if we have a tacit understanding,
attracting each otherظآز
ظآزWhen the loneliness cracks,
warmth seeps inظآز
ظآزYou come with light,
shining into my heartظآز
ظآزStars fall into my eyes,
and you fall into my heartظآز
ظآزI make a wish foolishly,
but actually, you are the shooting starظآز
ظآزOpen my secretظآز
ظآزI hope you find
all the tenderness hidden for youظآز
ظآزSinking into your love,
I want to sink deeperظآز
ظآزWith each breath,
I can feel the sweetnessظآز
ظآزTwo lonely islands meet,
and it's the gift of fateظآز